RG 005:038, Office of the Governor: Lowell P. Weicker, Jr. (1991-1995)
Connecticut State Library
- Series 2. Press Files, 1991-1994; 1995-031
  - Gov. Weicker names Donald Miller as Revenue Services Commissioner, 1993 December 8 (Box 4, Folder 71)
  - Connecticut Development Authority (CDA) press releases Bond Commission, 1993 December 10 (Box 4, Folder 72)
  - Summary and chronology of Office of Policy and Management (OPM) analytical work for the Governor, Department of Motor Vehicles (DMV) enhanced emissions program, 1993 December 10 (Box 4, Folder 73)
  - A. Searle Field, Chief of Staff to Gov. Weicker, Enhanced motor vehicle emissions test contract preferred bidder issues, 1993 December 14 (Box 4, Folder 74)
  - Camillone named acting Dept. of Motor Vehicles (DMV) Commissioner, 1993 December 16 (Box 4, Folder 75)
  - Gov. Weicker statement on Commissioner Goldberg, 1993 December 16 (Box 4, Folder 76)
  - Reward letter for murder of Elizabeth Rhinehart, 1993 December 17 (Box 4, Folder 77)
  - Reward letter for murder of Frances Gallo, 1993 December 17 (Box 4, Folder 78)
  - Special election 26th District, February 1, 1994, New Britain, 1993 December 17 (Box 4, Folder 79)
  - Nancy Hadley named Dept. of Motor Vehicles (DMV) Commissioner, 1993 December 20 (Box 4, Folder 80)
  - Council for Latino and Puerto Rican Affairs, 1993 December 22 (Box 4, Folder 81)
  - Reward letter for murder of Jacqueline Reynolds, 1993 December 22 (Box 4, Folder 82)
  - Statement of Gov. Lowell P. Weicker on investigation, 1993 December 22 (Box 4, Folder 83)
  - Welfare reform waiver letter, 1993 December 22 (Box 4, Folder 84)
  - State proposes welfare reform demonstration projects, time limit on benefits to receive New Haven test, 1993 December 27 (Box 4, Folder 85)
  - Gov. Weicker names Dr. Lenworth Jacobs to University of Connecticut Board of Trustees and appoints two to Judicial Selection Committee, 1993 December 28 (Box 4, Folder 86)
  - School based health clinics receive foundation grant, 1993 December 28 (Box 4, Folder 87)
  - State tourism study, 1993 December 28 (Box 4, Folder 88)
  - Gov. Weicker's New Year message 1993, 1993 December 30 (Box 4, Folder 89)
  - Gov. Weicker's significant accomplishments 1991-1993, undated (Box 4, Folder 90)
  - 1995 Special Olympics World Games announces Knights of Columbus partnership, 1994 January 5 (Box 4, Folder 91)
  - Gov. Weicker and state labor coalition announce landmark agreement on pay equity, 1994 January 12 (Box 4, Folder 92)
  - Gov. Weicker and state legislators unveil proposals aimed at curbing gun violence and illegal gun possession, 1994 January 13 (Box 4, Folder 93)
  - Gov. Weicker names Robert McKean as chair of Health and Educational Facilities Authority, 1994 January 14 (Box 4, Folder 94)
  - Gov. Weicker commencement address University of New Haven, 1994 January 15 (Box 4, Folder 95)
  - Statement to citizens of Bridgeport, 1994 January 18 (Box 4, Folder 96)
  - Gov. Weicker appoints 26 members to Blue Ribbon Commission on the Future of the Library, 1994 January 19 (Box 4, Folder 97)
  - Take a parent to school day, 1994 January 19 (Box 4, Folder 98)
  - Gov. Weicker and People's Bank announce loan program for persons with disabilities to purchase equipment, 1994 January 21 (Box 4, Folder 99)
  - Gov. Weicker statement on New England Patriots, 1994 January 21 (Box 4, Folder 100)
  - Remarks of Gov. Weicker on bio-technology summit, 1994 January 24 (Box 4, Folder 101)
  - Douglas E. Quat named Dept. of Environmental Protection (DEP) press secretary, 1994 January 24 (Box 4, Folder 102)
  - Janet Polinsky named Dept. of Administrative Services (DAS) Commissioner, 1994 January 26 (Box 4, Folder 103)
  - London Fog Corp. to relocate to Connecticut, 1994 January 26 (Box 4, Folder 104)
  - Gov. Weicker statement on Aetna, 1994 January 28 (Box 4, Folder 105)
  - Gov. Weicker names L.C. Heist of Greenwich to University of Connecticut Board of Trustees, appoints William Large to Judicial Review Council, 1994 January 28 (Box 4, Folder 106)
  - Gov. Weicker mid-term budget adjustments, primer, 1994 February (Box 4, Folder 107)
  - Press Releases Bond Commission meeting, 1994 February 2 (Box 4, Folder 108)
  - Health care reform, 1994 February 4 (Box 4, Folder 109)
  - A. Searle Field testimony before Transportation Committee, 1994 February 8 (Box 4, Folder 110)
  - Gov. Weicker announces new initiative to help children, increased funding for prisons, 1994 February 9 (Box 4, Folder 111)
  - Gov Weicker proposal elimination of personal property tax, 1994 February 9 (Box 4, Folder 112)
  - Dept. of Social Services, summary of budget 1994-1995, 1994 February 9 (Box 4, Folder 113)
  - Gov. Weicker statement regarding Vincent Ferrandino, 1994 February 10 (Box 4, Folder 114)
  - Donald Pogue named chair of Hospital Commission; Governor names Gary Smart to fill vacancy, 1994 February 14 (Box 4, Folder 115)
  - Opening of Smith Barney Shearson Training Center in Hartford, 1994 February 22 (Box 4, Folder 116)
  - Gov. Weicker statement on West Haven bond investment grade by Moody's Investor, 1994 February 25 (Box 4, Folder 117)
  - Claudia Weicker statement before the Select Committee on Children, 1994 March 1 (Box 4, Folder 118)
  - Gov. Weicker statement before the Select Committee on Children, 1994 March 1 (Box 4, Folder 119)
  - Gov. Weicker's youth initiative 1994-1995, undated (Box 4, Folder 120)
  - Affirmitive Action plan, Governor's Office, 1994 March 1 (Box 4, Folder 121)
  - Claudia and Gov. Weicker extend public invitation to tour executive residence, 1994 March 3 (Box 4, Folder 122)
  - Statement from Gov. Weicker on Attorney General's report on emissions contract, 1994 March 10 (Box 4, Folder 123)
  - Gov. Weicker announces appointments, 1994 March 11 (Box 4, Folder 124)
  - Gov. Weicker completes emissions review, Department of Motor Vehicles (DMV) Commissioner reaches agreement with Envirotest, 1994 March 15 (Box 4, Folder 125)
  - Enhanced emissions test cost to the consumer, 1994 March 15 (Box 4, Folder 126)
  - Chronology, 1994 March 15 (Box 4, Folder 127)
  - Memo to Gov. Weicker from Bruce Carlson and Maryann Palmarozza, 1994 March 15 (Box 4, Folder 128)
  - Letter to George Singleton, President, Envirotest Systems Corp., 1994 March 15 (Box 4, Folder 129)
  - Gov. Weicker statement on emissions, 1994 March 15 (Box 4, Folder 130)
  - Dept. of Motor Vehicles (DMV) emissions packet, 1994 March 15 (Box 4, Folder 131)
  - State reaches agreement to purchasing site for expanded University of Connecticut-Stamford branch, 1994 March 15 (Box 4, Folder 132)
  - ESP letter to Gov. Weicker, 1994 March 16 (Box 4, Folder 133)
  - Reward letter for murder of Lisa Distassio, 1994 March 17 (Box 4, Folder 134)
  - Reward letter for murder of Maria Perez, 1994 March 17 (Box 4, Folder 135)
  - Reward letter for murder of Minnie Sutton, 1994 March 17 (Box 4, Folder 136)
  - Reward letter for murder of Jane Doe, 1994 March 17 (Box 4, Folder 137)
  - Reward letter for murder of Elizabeth Gandy, 1994 March 17 (Box 4, Folder 138)
  - Reward letter for murder of Pamela Safford, 1994 March 17 (Box 4, Folder 139)
  - Reward letter for murder of John Toddoni, 1994 March 17 (Box 4, Folder 140)
  - Dept. of Environmental Protection (DEP) Bond Commission press release, 1994 March 23 (Box 4, Folder 141)
  - Dept. of Environmental Protection (DEP) Bond Commission press release, $1.9 million for economic development and job training, 1994 March 23 (Box 4, Folder 142)
  - Gov. Weicker announces new agreement between state, U.S. Marshals service to house federal prisoners, 1994 March 24 (Box 4, Folder 143)
  - Bill signed terminating the uncompensated care pool, 1994 March 31 (Box 4, Folder 144)
  - Bill signed, 1994 April 7 (Box 4, Folder 145)
  - Gov. Weicker nominates Allan B. Taylor to State Board of Education, Maria Mojica to Board of Governors for Higher Education, 1994 April 8 (Box 4, Folder 146)
  - Gov. Weicker statement on his personal income tax, 1994 April 18 (Box 4, Folder 147)
  - Bills signed, 1994 April 19 (Box 4, Folder 148)
  - Maria Cone nominated to Superior Court, 1994 April 20 (Box 4, Folder 149)
  - Gov. Weicker presented with Nogi Award, 1994 April 21 (Box 4, Folder 150)
  - Gov. Weicker statement on death of President Nixon, 1994 April 22 (Box 4, Folder 151)
  - Bills signed, 1994 May 2 (Box 4, Folder 152)
  - Letter to Carmen Diaz regarding Jim Gaudreau, intern, 1994 May 4 (Box 4, Folder 153)
  - Gov. Weicker is arrested I protest at embassy, 1994 May 5 (Box 4, Folder 154)
  - Bills signed, 1994 May 5 (Box 4, Folder 155)
  - Guns for Goods Program Finance Advisory Committee (FAC) meeting, 1994 May 5 (Box 4, Folder 156)
  - Gov. Weicker names Douglas E. Quat a press secretary; Avice Meehan to join staff of memorial Sloan-Kettering, 1994 May 5 (Box 4, Folder 157)
  - Gov. Weicker appoints state boards and commissions, 1994 May 6 (Box 4, Folder 158)
  - Dept. of Agriculture acquires development rights to farms, 1994 May 10 (Box 4, Folder 159)
  - Bond Commission approves $5.5 million for lead pain, other housing initiatives, 1994 May 12 (Box 4, Folder 160)
  - State Bond Commission approves $7.1 million for Dept. of Economic Development (DED), 1994 May 12 (Box 4, Folder 161)
  - State Bond Commission approves $21.4 million to improve Long Island Sound water quality, 1994 May 13 (Box 4, Folder 162)
  - Gov. Weicker statement on Betti Tianti, 1994 May 16 (Box 4, Folder 163)
  - Gov Weicker statement on Attorney General's opinions on Mohegan compact, 1994 May 18 (Box 4, Folder 164)
  - Bills signed, 1994 May 19 (Box 4, Folder 165)
  - Bills signed, 1994 May 20 (Box 4, Folder 166)
  - Bills signed, 1994 May 23 (Box 4, Folder 167)
  - Bills signed, 1994 May 24 (Box 4, Folder 168)
  - Bills signed, 1994 May 25 (Box 4, Folder 169)
  - End of session / special session speech, 1994 May 25 (Box 4, Folder 170)
  - Death penalty, 1994 May 26 (Box 4, Folder 171)
  - Gov. Weicker Wesleyan commencement speech, 1994 May 29 (Box 4, Folder 172)
  - Connecticut Alliance for Home Ownership Opportunities, undated (Box 4, Folder 173)
  - Bills signed, #19, #20, #21, 1994 June 2 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Purchasing reform bill, 1994 June 4 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Bills signed, #23, 1994 June 6 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Bills signed, #24, 1994 June 7 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Bills signed, #25, 1994 June 8 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Gov. Weicker announces grants for youth programs in cities, 1994 June 9 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Veto message on H.B. 5852 #27 and bills signed #28, 1994 June 9 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Attorney General's report on Camp Weicker, 1994 June 10 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Bills signed #29, 1994 June 10 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Press release - Susan Shimelan, Office of Policy and Management (OPM), 1994 June 10 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Justice of the Peace, H.B.5069, 1994 June 11 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Gov. Weicker signs health care reform legislation, 1994 June 15 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Gov. Weicker announces state's selection of National Service programs, 1994 June 16 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Gov. Weicker appoints Suzette Benn chair of Health Care Access Office, 1994 June 23 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Dept. of Mental Health (DMH) report of the Ad Hoc Committee on the Insanity Defense, 1994 June 24 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Connecticut's Wetland restoration efforts to restore Milford salt marsh, 1994 June 24 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Gov. Weicker commencement speech Stafford High School, 1994 June 24 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Call of special session July 6, 1994 regarding firearms, 1994 June 24 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Press Releases Bond Commission meeting, 1994 June 24 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Gov. Weicker joins Pittsburgh Penguins Advisory Board, 1994 June 29 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Gun violence legislation, 1994 June 29 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Gov. Weicker announces third consecutive state surplus, 1994 June 30 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Bill signing #33, 1994 July 1 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Gov. Weicker announces appointments, 1994 July 6 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Gov. Weicker proclamation for special session regarding guns, 1994 July 6 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Bill signing #35, 1994 July 7 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Gov. Weicker announces rewards, 1994 July 8 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Technology grants, 1994 July 11 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Gov. Weicker announces grant for courthouse security, 1994 July 12 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Gov. Weicker approves reward, 1994 July 12 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Allan Fairbank named executive director of Office of Health Care Access (OHCA), 1994 July 13 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Bill signing #36, 1994 July 15 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Gov. Weicker joins Dresing Lierman, 1994 July 20 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Gov. Weicker statement on Groark / Rowe team, 1994 July 22 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Gov. Weicker statement on John J. Driscoll, 1994 July 22 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - A Connecticut Party nominating convention speech, 1994 July 23 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Gov. Weicker's reward approval, 1994 July 25 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Pat Giardi named Dept. of Social Services Commissioner, 1994 August 4 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Gov. Weicker announces youth center grants, 1994 August 5 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Gov. Weicker announces $169.3 million surplus for 1994, 1994 August 23 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Gov. Weicker authorizes reward for murder of Anson Clinton, 1994 August 26 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Bond Commission, 1994 August 26 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Gov. Weicker requests federal money for Litchfield company, 1994 August 29 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Gov. Weicker nominates 13 judges, 1994 September 1 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - National Alliance of Business names Connecticut State of the Year, 1994 September 1 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Rating Connecticut Development Authority (CDA) bonds, 1994 September 12 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Swiss Bank relocation, 1994 September 21 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Bond Commission, 1994 September 23 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Miles Inc. to expand in Orange, Conn., 1994 September 29 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Report, "For the record, " State of Connecticut, Gov. Lowell P. Weicker, 1994 September (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Proclamation by Gov. Weicker on banking, tax, Swiss Bank, appointment of judges to Superior and Appellate Courts, 1994 October (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - IMRS, Inc. to remain in Stamford, 1994 October 3 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Remarks from Colt's Manufacturing Company, 1994 October 3 (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Gov. Weicker cites U.S. Repeating Arms as positive sign for New Haven, 1994 October 17 (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Gov. Weicker announces appointments, 1994 October 17 (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - Release of signing the bill Swiss Bank, 1994 October 17 (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - Swiss Bank letter from Commissioner Joseph McGee, 1994 October 17 (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - Gov. Weicker announces kick-off of 1994 Care and Share Food Drive, 1994 October 18 (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - Gov. Weicker announces $11.7 million in grants for drug enforcement and educational programs, 1994 October 18 (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - Connecticut Dept. of Education release, Conn. Education Commissioner praises regional plans for education quality and diversity, 1994 October 19 (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - Gov. Weicker announces appointments, 1994 October 28 (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - Bond commission approves $9.5 million for housing initiatives, 1994 October 28 (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - Press release; State Bond Commission approves $19.1 million for urban site remediation, 1994 October 28 (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - Gov. Weicker announces storm aid to six towns, 1994 October 31 (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - Gov. Weicker announces two judges, 1994 November 22 (Box 5, Folder 65)
  - State - MetraHealth agreement, 1994 December 2 (Box 5, Folder 66)
  - West Haven Financial Review Board disbands, 1994 December 21 (Box 5, Folder 67)
  - WTA Tour moves to Stamford, 1994 December 21 (Box 5, Folder 68)
  - Videotapes (Box 6)
    - The 12 days of Christmas, News 12, Jim Murphy and Wayne Pellenberg, 1992 December 24 (Box 6)
    - Gov. Weicker's address, Connecticut Youth "Challenge" program graduation, 1993 December 22
  - Audiotapes
    - Gov. Weicker and Harrison Salisbury, 1992 August 26
    - Gov. Weicker and Harrison Salisbury, 1992 August 28
    - Reporter's notebook, Dana Dieterle, "Christmas at the Weickers", 1992 December 3
    - Education bill signing, Connecticut Award for Excellence, Pratt & Whitney labor agreement, banking industry press conference, pres conference on various issues, Tom Scott radio show WPOP on Governor's residence, undated
    - Gov. Weicker, unidentified, undated
  - Photographs
    - Gov. Weicker and others at ribbon cutting ceremony of the Dept. of Public Works, 12 color photographs, 3.5 x 5 in. (Sent to the Governor by Dept. of Public Works), undated
    - Gov. Weicker and others at an evening reception "Pre-opening of Histeria" (with cover letter from Dana & Jim Thompson, WGCH radio, Greenwich), 6 color photographs, 4 x 6 in., 1994 December
    - Gov. Weicker and others attending a reception held by Local 371, signed by Robert A. Petronella, President, 7 color photographs, 8.5 x 10 in., 1994 November
- Series 3. Invitations Accepted and Rejected, 1992-1993; 1995-040
  - Invitations accepted
    - 1993, undated (Box 55, Folder 1-23)
  - Invitations regretted
    - 1993 May-June (Box 56, Folder 1-23)
    - 1993 July-October 19 (Box 57, Folder 1-26)
    - 1993 October 20-December (Box 58, Folder 1-22)
  - Unpersonalized invitations, 1992 November-1993 August (Box 58, Folder 23-26)
  - Miscellaneous, 1993 April-November, undated (Box 58, Folder 27-29)
  - Cancelled events, 1993 (Box 58, Folder 30)
- Series 4. Official Statements, 1994; 1995-040
  - Official statements, 1994 (Box 59, Folder 1-20)
- Series 5. Legal Office, 1977-1994
  - Auditor's Reports
    - 1995-022
      - Administrative Services, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      - Agriculture, Dept. of, 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      - Arts/History, Commission on, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - CADAC (Box 1, Folder 4)
      - Chief State’s Attorney/Criminal Justice, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - Children and Families, Dept. of, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 6)
      - Children and Youth Services, Dept. of (Box 1, Folder 7)
      - Comptroller, Treasurer, Secretary of the State, Attorney General, 1992-1994 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      - Connecticut Innovations, 1992-1994 (Box 1, Folder 8)
      - Connecticut Resources Recovery Authority (CRRA), 1994 (Box 1, Folder 9)
      - Connecticut, State of, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 10)
      - Connecticut, State of, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      - Consumer Protection, Dept. of, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      - Corrections, Dept. of, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      - Economic Development, Dept. of, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      - Education, Dept. of, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 5)
      - Emergency Management, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 6)
      - Environmental Protection, Dept. of, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 7)
      - Ethics/FOI, 1992-1994 (Box 2, Folder 8)
      - Governor’s Office, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 9)
      - Health Services, Dept. of (Box 3, Folder 1)
      - Higher Education, Dept. of, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 2-4)
      - Higher Education, Dept. of, 1994 January-June 15 (Box 3, Folder 5-7)
      - Higher Education, Dept. of, 1994 June 16-December 31; 2 folders (Box 4, Folder 1-2)
      - Housing, Dept., 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 3)
      - Income Maintenance, Dept. of, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      - Insurance, Dept. of, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 5)
      - Labor, Dept. Of, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 6)
      - Legislative Management, Commission on, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 7)
      - Lieutenant Governor, Office of, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 8)
      - Liquor Control, Dept. of, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 9)
      - Mental Health, Dept. of, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 10)
      - Mental Retardation, Dept. of, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      - Military, Dept. of, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      - Miscellaneous, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      - Motor Vehicles, Dept. of, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      - Policy and Management, Office of, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      - Probate (Box 5, Folder 6)
      - Protection and Advocacy for Persons with Disabilities, Office of, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 7)
      - Public Defender Services, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 8)
      - Public Safety, Dept. of, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 9)
      - Public Utilities, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 10)
      - Public Works, Dept. of, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 11)
      - Revenue Services, Dept. of, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 12)
      - Social Services, Aging, Deaf and Hearing Impaired, Human Resources, Departments of, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 13)
      - Soldiers, Sailors and Maine Fund, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 1)
      - Special Revenue, Dept. of, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 2)
      - Statewide Emergency Telecommunications, Bureau of, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 3)
      - Thefts, Vandalism, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 4)
      - Transportation, Dept. of, 1993-1994 (Box 6, Folder 5)
      - Veterans Affairs, Dept. of, 1993-1994 (Box 6, Folder 6)
      - Victims Services, Office of (Judicial Department), 1994 (Box 6, Folder 7)
      - Wing Civil Air Patrol, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 8)
      - Worker’s Compensation, 1993-1994 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Agency Files, 1994 (Box 6)
    - 1995-022
      - Administrative Services, Dept. of, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 10)
      - Agriculture, Dept. of, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 11)
      - CADAC, 1990-1993 (Box 6, Folder 12)
      - CHEFA, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 13)
      - [Chief Medical Examiner, Office of], 1993-1994 (Box 6, Folder 14)
      - Consumer Protection, Dept. of, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 15)
      - Corrections, Dept. of, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 16)
      - Development Authority, Connecticut, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 17)
      - Education, Dept. of, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 18)
      - Ethics Commission/[Lobbyists], 1992-1993 (Box 6, Folder 19)
      - Firearms Permit Examiners, Board of], 1993-1994 (Box 6, Folder 20)
      - Fire Prevention and Control, Commission on, 1993-1994 (Box 7, Folder 1)
      - Health Services, Dept. of, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 2)
      - Higher Education, Connecticut Board of Governors, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      - Higher Education, Dept. of, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 4)
      - Hospitals and Health Care, Commission on, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      - Housing, Dept. of, 1991-1994 (Box 7, Folder 6)
      - [Housing Finance Authority, Connecticut], 1992 (Box 7, Folder 7)
      - Human Resources, Dept. of, 1991-1992 (Box 7, Folder 8)
      - Human Rights and Opportunities, Commission on Affirmative Action (Box 7)
        - Folder I, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 9)
        - Folder II (Box 8, Folder 1)
        - Executive Director, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 2)
        - [Miscellaneous], 1992-1993 (Box 8, Folder 3)
        - Task Force, 1988, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 4)
      - Income Maintenance, Teresa Hines, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 5)
      - Information Technology, Office of, 1992, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 6)
      - Insurance, Dept. of, 1990-1994 (Box 8, Folder 7)
      - Judicial [Dept.], 1991-1994 (Box 8, Folder 8)
      - Labor, Dept. of (Box 8)
        - [Employment Security Board of Review], 1990 (Folder 9)
        - Hamden Job Center, 1992-1993 (Box 9, Folder 1)
        - [Miscellaneous], 1988-1994 (Box 9, Folder 2-3)
        - Unemployment Compensation, 1991-1992 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - Law Revision Commission, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 5)
      - Library, State, 1993-1994 (Box 9, Folder 6)
      - Liquor Control, Dept. of, 1990-1994 (Box 9, Folder 7)
      - Mental Health, Dept. of, 1991-1993 (Box 9, Folder 8)
      - Mental Retardation, Dept. of, 1991-1994 (Box 9, Folder 9)
      - Military Department, 1980-1992 (Box 9, Folder 10)
      - Motor Vehicles, Dept. of, 1988-1993 (Box 9, Folder 11)
      - Municipal Police Training Council, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 1)
      - Pardons, Board of, 1991-1994 (Box 10, Folder 2)
      - Policy and Management, Office of, 1992-1994 (Box 10, Folder 3)